Modern women are busy with work
The proportion of late marriage and late childbirth
is increasing
Many people wait until they are 35
to get pregnant.
But found
Premature ovarian failure
Egg quality has deteriorated
As a result, it became extremely difficult to get pregnant
and have children
Why do some people
have such an easy pregnancy?
But some people have it so hard.
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I'm your old friend, Dr. Hu.
I want to share with you today
3 warning signs of ovarian aging
The habit that hurts your ovaries the most is this
Eat this way to prevent premature ovarian failure
Note 3 Foods that Kill Sperm
May cause infertility
Whether you are single or married
Want to have children
Or women who do not want to have children
I recommend you to watch this episode
Love this episode
Please help me share
To your female friends
Ovarian aging and premature failure 10 years
Pay attention to 3 warning signs
What are the symptoms of premature ovarian failure
Now, can you follow what I'm saying
and
take a little test together?
See if you have these
three warning signs
1. Menstrual abnormalities
2. Symptoms of menopause appear early
3. Not enough hormones
1. Menstrual abnormalities
Irregular periods and less menstrual blood
Even if they don't report for more than 4 months
2. Early onset of menopausal symptoms
Hot flashes and night sweats
Mood swings and poor sleep
3. Hormone deficiency
Vaginal dryness and decreased libido
bones ache too.
Loose skin
If you are under 40
If any
of the symptoms mentioned
above occur
See a doctor immediately
Take care of your ovaries
It's protecting your youth
and protect your health
and options to protect your future
Married and unmarried ladies
Please pay attention
Premature ovarian aging
At 35,
look like 45.
gestures
A strong smell of auntie
The worst thing
is that when you go to a class reunion,
you are 10 years older than your classmates.
Not only that
When you meet Mr. Right
Or when you are getting older
and want to get pregnant
and have children
However, premature ovarian aging was found
Want to conceive
It becomes more difficult
What hurts your ovaries most is not age
But it
Rome wasn't built in a day
Ovaries don't age overnight.
These four little habits
will steal your ovarian function bit by bit
1. Staying up late for a long time
2. Cold inside and outside
3. Sitting for long periods of time and wearing tight pants
4. Pressure is bursting
How many did you win?
No. 1
The worst habit that harms your ovaries is
Staying up late for a long time
You said Dr. Hu
I don't go to bed until one or two o'clock every day
Nothing at all
Don't be like this
It's not that won't take revenge, it's just that the time hasn't come yet.
11pm to 3pm is the golden time
for liver and gallbladder repair.
You're not sleeping yet
It's constantly operating
Ovaries, the generator of youth
Keep working like this
It would be strange if ovarian function didn't get worse.
Jolin Tsai
can lie down at 9:30.
She said when she got up
Become super beautiful
You just need to
Go to bed 10 minutes earlier
You slowly adjust to going to bed
before 11pm
That way you will
More and more beautiful
Internal and external cold
Ovaries are frozen
You drink all your drinks ice cold.
Also likes to wear short tops to show off waist
Be careful,
this will cause the cold air to flow directly
into your lower abdomen
Freeze your ovaries
The cold has been invading for a long time
period comes or goes
She got mad at you.
Menstrual flow is getting less and less and late
Then, dysmenorrhea
Even affecting fertility
Come
Two ways to warm up the ovaries
1. Eat less or no ice cream, salad, or sashimi
2. Use warm water when taking a shower every day
Rinse your abdomen
Rinse for about two minutes
A small action
Warms the entire ovary and uterus
No. 3
Sitting still all day
Love wearing tight pants
People wearing body shapers
Your pelvic cavity is blocked.
Qi and blood stagnation
It is easy to have more leucorrhea
Menstrual blood is not fully discharged.
You can do this
Sit for an hour
Just stand up and walk for a few minutes
About three minutes
By the way, press the sān yīn jiāo(transliteration) acupoint
Where is the sān yīn jiāo(transliteration) acupoint?
Above the ankle
About four fingers
Unblock the Qi and blood
Gynecological care
The fourth
Pressure is bursting
Liver Qi stagnation
Long-term emotional depression and anxiety
It will cause liver qi stagnation
Qi and blood flow disorder
Cause endocrine disorders
Irregular menstruation and unstable ovulation
Afternoon tea with a cup of rose tea
Help you promote blood circulation and relieve liver
There is also a floral scent
Just smell it and your anxiety will be relieved
If you have two
or more of these four habits
Pay attention
Adjust yourself starting today
Stay away from gynecological diseases
5 types and 10 categories
5 types of food to eat
Save the ovaries from premature failure
Want to prevent ovarian aging
Call it the Immortal
You must take good care of your spleen and kidneys
Shèn cáng jīng zhǔ guǎn shēng zhí (transliteration)
The energy source for the ovaries
The spleen is the foundation of acquired constitution
Responsible for converting food into qi and blood
Supplying kidneys and ovaries
Sufficient kidney qi and strong spleen
The ovum will develop healthily and mature
Stay away from premature aging
How to take good care of your spleen and stomach
Don't eat too salty
Don't eat too spicy food
Don't eat too much oil
Don't eat too much ice, etc.
These foods
Don't get hungry either.
Don't eat too much.
Provide the most comfortable environment for the spleen and stomach
To transfer nutrients
to your ovaries
How to take good care of your kidneys
You can
Black food tastes good
Black into the kidney
Can replenish shèn jīng(transliteration) and nourish ovaries
Black sesame, black beans, and black fungus
Eat it up
Another thing
to take care of your kidneys
is to get regular rest.
Don't go to bed too late
Too much rest
Come again
The two ovaries' favorite foods
Eat it up
1. Soy products
Soy milk, tofu, miso
They all contain soy isoflavones
Also called phytoestrogen
Anti-oxidation and anti-aging
2. Folic Acid
Spinach, sweet potato leaves, amaranth
They can replenish blood and nourish qi
Helps smooth ovulation
You are a woman who is trying to conceive
Two types of food are good for you
1. Foods rich in Coenzyme Q10
Olive Oil Walnuts Beef
Helping ovum
Able to become strong and energetic
2. Foods containing vitamin D3
Eat mushroom milk
Plus get some sun every day
Probably about 10 minutes.
Tonifies Qi and Yang.
Better ovarian follicle development
You take good care of your Ovum
What about your other half?
Also needs to be supplemented together.
Want to be a father?
3 Foods that kill sperm may cause infertility
Young people who want to have a baby
You must know
The key to determining the baby's gender
It's sperm
Are the sperm healthy?
A lot depends
on your eating habits
Danish research survey
Nearly 3,000 men
It was found
that people who frequently ate fried
processed meats and sugary drinks
The number of sperm
On average, only 26 million
In the long run
It's not just the declining fertility rate
Maybe even
will never be a father.
A man who loves chicken cutlets, hot dogs and cola
Hey, eat and drink less.
The good news
is that there is still hope.
Start by eating a Mediterranean diet
Eat more vegetables
whole grains and fish
It can not only increase the number of sperm
Vitality and quality can be improved
The other two behaviors
It will reduce sperm
1. Take a hot bath frequently
Or often in a high temperature environment
Reduce sperm count
Over 37 degrees
Did you know
Sperm will not survive well.
Second, wearing pants that are too tight.
It will also make it too hot.
So
It also hinders the production of sperm
Having a baby at 40
Difficulty getting pregnant and spending over a million
A while ago
I met a 40-year-old lady.
I have been praying for a child for almost 10 years.
But there is no movement
It really makes people anxious.
I've seen too many things like this
really advise all parents
who want to have children.
Take good care of your body
Get pregnant early
Have a baby early
There are 4 benefits
No need for ovulation injections
No need to freeze ovum
High pregnancy success rate
It can save you millions
Do you know
the success rate of IVF?
Under 35 years old
The IVF success rate is 60%.
50% before age 40
After 40, less than 30%
Will it cost millions?
Let me help you calculate
older women
One test tube costs about 200,000
Do it at least 3 to 4 times
The cost is really over a million.
I also want to remind you
The older you are when you have a child
the more it
will affect the child's future health.
I'll share a story with you
There are two people in winter
Walking in the snow
When the old man crossed the river
Not afraid of the cold at all
Calm demeanor
On the contrary, the young man
Shivering and feeling cold
Why is this young man less physically fit
than the old man?
The reason is
The elderly are born when their parents were young.
Abundant energy
Young people are born
when their parents
are very old.
Congenitally weak constitution
Did you know
This story
Recorded in the Investiture of the Gods
It says that the two brothers are walking
in different situations.
Pregnancy at an advanced age
First, adjust these three issues
The infertility rate in Taiwan is 10% to 15%.
One in seven couples
has difficulty conceiving
Want to successfully prepare for pregnancy
Take good care of your kidneys, spleen, and liver
Three types of physiques that are not easy to win the lottery
Type 1: Kidney Deficiency
Traditional Chinese Medicine says the kidneys control reproduction.
Once kidney deficiency
It's like the fuel tank is empty and the engine won't start.
Causes women to have less menstrual flow
Delayed menstruation is a warning sign
Type 2: Qi and blood deficiency
You often feel tired
Poor complexion and scanty menstruation
Have you even had a miscarriage?
This is mostly caused by spleen deficiency.
Traditional Chinese medicine believes that the spleen
Wéi qì xuè shēng huà zhī yuán(transliteration)
The spleen is like a nutrient factory
Qi and blood cannot be generated
The embryo has no nutrients to implant.
And the muscles
of the uterus need to nurture the embryo.
It is also controlled by the spleen
The embryo has no nutrients to implant and develop.
It's hard to get pregnant naturally
Type 3:Gān yù(transliteration)
Before your period
Will there be
Breast tenderness
Irregular menstrual periods
High stress can easily lead to liver qi stagnation
Causes no ovulation and no implantation.
If you have any of these
Be sure to adjust as early as possible
To successfully get pregnant